AttestRWA — Settlement Attestation Layer for RWA
On-chain compliance bridge for stablecoin settlements
Booting the demo stack — Anvil fork of Base Sepolia
EAS protocol bytecode at canonical 0x4200…0021
SettlementEscrow + MockUSDC deployed to local fork
FastAPI attester live · Next.js web · stack ready
Happy path — Buyer deposits 580 mock USDC
Off-chain attester decides and signs EAS attestation
Decision APPROVE — payee verified, capital green
Escrow releases — payee receives 580 USDC
Reject path — agent points to impostor SRL Holding 2026
Attester signs attestation with payeeVerified = false
Escrow refuses release — audit trail recorded on-chain
Buyer is refunded — impostor receives nothing
Real EAS bytecode at the canonical Base address
4,121 bytes — production code, not a mock
Open source · Apache-2.0 · github.com/FUYOH666